The Prime Minister himself is going to hold a meeting at 3:00 PM.
Now the market will keep an eye on the updates after 3 PM. We will be
in tomorrow morning but
overall the market will want to pay attention to how to
handle the situation from here and
what kind of stars are seen forming for that.
Our experts are ready with their trends for the government's speech.
Prakash Gaba, Gaurav
Vishwa, Prashant Sagar, Sharmila Joshi will
tell you what strategy you have to adopt
today and of course your focus should be on this. In
fact, we will also do an industry check on the
hotel sector because this is where the
biggest decline was seen yesterday. Indian
Hotels. Pressure was seen in all other companies.
This is the impact of the Covid tax. On one hand, it is
for the peak season end and on the other hand, this
rate of Covid. So, in such a situation, what different preparations will have to be done
and how is the demand situation at this time.
Vishal Kamat,
Director of Kamat Group of Hotels, is going to join us on this today.
Not only this, today we will also include SIM in the program.
He also has an interesting news
on cost and the market action will be
discussed. But let's open the floor and
take the trend at this time.  Let's start
afternoon tell me what trade you have in hand that
is ICICI General Insurance it seems we can get a
bounce from here and it is possible that we can get it, I will
channel here like this that
now Bank Nifty makes a
cut above its call writer of 42500, let's take a call on this quickly
Prashant good afternoon Prashant,
call writer of 42500 traveling to
catch a call did
you say right now my opinion was that if
a turn comes against the call writers of 42200 then
maybe a big turn can be upset but
I would not like to take any trade right now so
I will not take any trade in the expiry for the last van over
and I will only
consider it a pool bag on this, no change of train, I will only wait
and watch,
I am doing the shorting so see commentary
no direction all the
stocks that came up in the pharma sector, in
this the stock which made a base and
came up after making a higher bottom and is up after consultation is the
disease slab all the other
stocks came up in a day if you waited a little then
I  I would like to go with Divas Lab,
it is currently around 3,500.
In the spot, I will take a risk of 3470 i.e. around 1% here
and my target will be the
average of two days, basically, i.e., I am
looking at a target around 3770.50, if it is justified then
this trend will be mine.